<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="bug_report_private_policy">Dear users,\r\nCoolpad Group and its affiliates ("Coolpad" or "we/our/us") value your privacy and personal data. Please do not submit any personal or private data to Coolpad before you comprehensively read, understand, and agree to this Policy. \r\n

\nThis Policy is intended to help you understand the following: \r\n
1. How Coolpad collects and uses your personal data; \r\n
2. How Coolpad uses cookies, beacons and similar technologies; \r\n
3. How Coolpad discloses your personal data; \r\n
4. How to modify, change, or check your personal data; \r\n
5. How Coolpad protects your personal data; \r\n
6. How Coolpad protects the personal data of children; \r\n
7. Disclaimer; \r\n
8. Update of this Policy; \r\n
9. Contact us. \r\n

\nPlease note that this Privacy Policy applies to the devices, websites, online application or services of Coolpad citing or linking to this Policy, and the consumer-level electronic products of Coolpad, including but not limited to feature phones, smartphones, home devices, data cards, tablets, mobile phones or computer applications, tools and software, and relevant websites, products, and services. This Policy does not apply to Coolpad websites, services, and products that do not display or link to this Policy or those that have their own Privacy Policies. \r\n

\nThis Policy describes how Coolpad handles personal and private data and how Coolpad is committed to protecting your privacy. However, one policy may not be expansive enough to address all concerns of data processing. Therefore, Coolpad may provide additional information that is specific to a product or service as a supplement to this Policy in order to keep you informed about other data collection purposes. Please note such notices in other forms during the use of Coolpad products or services. Please read this Privacy Policy and its supplementary terms carefully. By using of our devices, websites or online applications, services or the consumer-level electronic products of Coolpad, you agree to this Privacy Policy and its supplementary terms. \r\n

\n<b>1. How Coolpad collects and uses your personal data?</b>\r\n1.1. How, when, and for what purposes does Coolpad collect and make use of your personal data? \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tIf you submit requests online to create an account or to purchase or register our products or services, we may ask you to provide information, such as your email address, delivery address, phone number, product information, time of purchase, and method of payment to implement your purchase orders, deliver your products or services, provide technical support or updates, and more. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tWhen you are participating in promotions or market surveys held by Coolpad, we may ask you to provide relevant information, such as your phone number and email address, to contact you, send you information about products and services that you may be interested in or invite you to our promotions and market surveys upon your agreement. You may reject or turn off such options on our websites, prompt windows or our products, or visit www.coolpad.com to contact us, to refuse Coolpad to use your personal data for promotions or market surveys. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tIf you use our services to share content with your friends or invite your friends to participate in, we may need you to provide your friends\' contact information, including but not limited to any SNS accounts and email addresses. Coolpad may use such information to send invitations to your friends by email, instant messages, SNS, or SMS/MMS. The information will only be used for the purpose of sending invitations. Coolpad will not save this information or use such information for other purposes. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tCoolpad may collect system and application data from your devices in order to inform you about available system or application updates. Such information may include your device name, system and application versions, operating system and browser versions, region and language settings, device identification numbers (IMEI, ESN, MEID, and SN), and your service provider\'s network ID, MAC address, IP address and the settings of the device accessing services. Coolpad processes such information for the sole purpose of informing you about system or application updates. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tCoolpad may collect certain information for statistics and analysis, including your device name, device version, device identification numbers (IMEI, ESN, MEID, and SN), the fuzzy geographic location information of your device (such as the ID of the area where your device is located), your service provider\'s network ID (PLMN), how you use your applications, and the IP address you use to access the Internet. Coolpad collects and processes such information to provide you with the best personalized user experience and to customize content, improve our products, analyze the efficiency of our business operations, analyze our market share, improve the security of Coolpad\'s networks and services, and activate your after-sale services. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tIf your device or application experiences any errors, you can choose to send the error information to Coolpad so that Coolpad and Coolpad\'s partners can provide you with troubleshooting services. Coolpad may collect relevant information about the issue, such as your device model, application name and version, device identification number, and error logs. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tSome of the services that Coolpad provides allow you to synchronize, share, and store data. Coolpad may collect and store data that you upload or download and data required to implement the uploads and downloads. \r\n

\n1.2. Location-based services\r\nWhen you access certain location-based services, for example, when you search for information, navigate, or check the weather based on specific locations, Coolpad may collect, use, and process the precise or fuzzy location information of your device. This is to allow Coolpad to provide the preceding services for you. Information collected may include your device identification numbers, type, model, and real-time location information (including that obtained through GPS, WLAN, and your service provider\'s network ID). You may turn on/off the GPS from GPS settings. However, due to your service provider\’s policy, you may not have the right to control WLAN and select mobile network. Coolpad collects location information anonymously to provide and improve location-based products and services. \r\n

\n1.3. Collection and use of non-personal information\r\n"Non-personal information" refers to information that cannot be used to identify a specific person. Coolpad may collect aggregate statistical information, such as the number of visitors to our website and the click-through rate of webpages. Coolpad collects such information to understand how people use our website, products, or services. In this way, Coolpad can improve our services to better meet customers\’ needs. Coolpad may, at its own discretion, collect, use, transfer, or disclose non-personal information for other purposes. \r\n

\n<b>2. How Coolpad uses cookies, beacons and similar technologies</b>\r\nCoolpad and some third parties providing content, advertisement or other functions through products or services of Coolpad may use cookies, beacons and other similar technologies within the scope of services. By accessing and using our products or services, you agree to our storing cookies, other local storage technologies, beacons and other information on your device, and in addition, you agree to the access of such information by Coolpad and the above-mentioned third parties. \r\n

\n<b>3. How Coolpad discloses your personal data</b>\r\nCoolpad will never sell your personal data to third parties without your knowledge. However, Coolpad may disclose your personal data in the following situations: \r\n
3.1. After obtaining your approval, Coolpad may share your personal information with other companies; Coolpad will never sell your personal data to third parties for their own marketing or commercial purposes without your permission. \r\n

\n3.2. Coolpad may need to provide you with certain services through some cooperating parties. Therefore, Coolpad may share some of your personal information with cooperating parties to enrich our services and improve your overall experience. For example, when you decide to purchase Coolpad products online, Coolpad will need to submit your personal information to relevant logistic service providers to allow them to deliver the products to you, or allow our cooperating parties to provide you with other services. Coolpad forbids all Coolpad subsidiaries or authorized third parties to use shared personal information for any other purposes. \r\n

\n3.3. Coolpad may disclose your personal information when required by the law, legal proceedings, litigation, or public, governmental authorities. \r\n

\n3.4. Your personal information may also be disclosed to transaction parties under circumstances that Coolpad is involved in reorganization, merger, or insolvency liquidation. \r\n

\n3.5. Your personal information may be disclosed to relevant parties for the protection of rights, properties or safety of Coolpad and its affiliates, partners or customers. \r\n

\n3.6. Coolpad may disclose your personal information for maintenance of social public interests. \r\n

\n<b>4. How to modify, change, or check your personal data</b>\r\nYou will be responsible for the accuracy of the personal information you submit. Coolpad makes the best commercial endeavor to keep the accuracy of your personal information, and Coolpad will delete or amend the information upon your request. You can contact Cool Cloud, our cloud service provider, and make request by calling Cool Cloud hotline at 029-88824132 or visiting www.coolyun.com. Under the terms and conditions of Coolpad, you can manage your personal information at any time, such as your personal account registration information. \r\n

\n<b>5. How Coolpad protects your personal data</b>\r\nCoolpad takes reasonable preventive measures, including but not limited to, technical, physical, and regulatory actions to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, disclosure, use, change, damage, or loss. For example, from a technical perspective, Coolpad uses anti-virus software to encrypt and monitor our systems and protect data centers from malicious attacks. From a physical perspective, Coolpad has set in place visit control mechanisms, allowing only authorized personnel to access some personal data. From a regulatory perspective, Coolpad makes sure employees understand the importance of protecting personal data through training sessions on security and privacy protection awareness. Although we take the utmost care to protect your personal data, please note that no websites, internet transfer, computer system, terminal storage and transfer or wireless connection are absolutely secure. \r\n

\n<b>6. How Coolpad protects the personal data of children</b>\r\nCoolpad\’s products or services may contain content suitable for children. Unless required by law, Coolpad will not collect any personal data from children at the age of 13 or under on purpose without seeking prior parental consent. We will delete it according to applicable laws once we get to know that the personal data provider is at the age of 13 or under. \r\n

\n<b>7. Disclaimer</b>\r\n7.1.To ensure an efficient visit and improve user experience, you may be provided with web hyperlinks or services from third parties, over which Coolpad does not have control. Coolpad undertakes no responsibility for the safety or privacy of any personal data collected by these web hyperlinks or services. You can choose whether to access such hyperlinks or content or use services and products of these third parties. Coolpad cannot control any privacy and data protection measures of third parties, and such measures will not be governed by this Policy either. This Policy does not apply to any information that you voluntarily provide to third parties. Please refer to the privacy protection policies of the third parties instead. \r\n

\n7.2.Coolpad products and services may be provided using resources and servers located in various countries and regions around the world. Therefore, your personal information may be transferred across international borders outside the country where you use our services. Those countries may not have laws providing specific protection for personal data, or they may have different legal regulations on data protection. In such cases, Coolpad will ensure that there is a legal basis for such transfers and that adequate protection for your personal data is provided as required by applicable laws. \r\n

\n<b>8. Update of this Policy</b>\r\nCoolpad may update or amend this Policy from time to time. Coolpad will notify you of the changes upon update of this Policy. You may also visit our website to inquire the latest version of this Policy. By using of our devices, websites or online applications, services or the consumer-level electronic products of Coolpad after the update of this Policy, you agree to the updated Policy. \r\n

\n<b>9. Contact us</b>\r\nThe copyright of this Policy belongs to the Coolpad Group. Coolpad Group reserves the right to interpret and change it. If you have any questions, comments, or suggestions on our products, please submit them by calling customer service hotline at 4008881388 or visiting www.coolpad.com.</string>
    <string name="bug_report_user_potocol">Dear users,\r\nThe User Agreement (the “Agreement”) is entered into among you (or “User”, refers to all individuals or organizations who register, log in, use or browse our Services), Coolpad Group, and its affiliates (“Coolpad” or “we/our/us”) and our operational cooperators (“Cooperator”), with respect to Coolpad websites www.coolpad.com (“Site”) and the products, programs and services (“Services”) of Coolpad.\r\n

\nPlease read carefully and fully understand this Agreement, including the terms of Disclaimer of Warranty, Limitation of Liability, and Rights and Limitations, and choose to accept or not to accept this Agreement (minors should read this Agreement accompanied by legal guardian). Coolpad may suspend or stop providing our Services to you if you do not comply with our terms or policies. By your registration, login, usage of the Services or other actions, you acknowledge that you have read and understood, and agree to accept and be bound by the terms and conditions of this Agreement. \r\n

\nBy accepting this Agreement, you agree to accept all constraints, including accepting Coolpad to reserve the right to modify and update the terms of this Agreement from time to time, without notice to you. The updated terms shall supersede any previous terms. You can visit our website to check the latest User Agreement. If you cannot accept any content that we have changed, you shall stop using Coolpad Services. By your continued use of our Services, you agree to accept and will be bound by the modified terms of this Agreement. \r\n

\n<b>1. Terms of Usage of Our Services</b>\r\n1.1. You may visit the Site without registration. However, you need a Cool Cloud Account (“Account”) and provide relevant personal information on the registration webpage in order to access more Site functions and Services. Any changes in your personal information must be updated timely. You shall be responsible for all results arising from inaccurate or untrue information provided. You can delete or suspend your account under the instructions of the Site, and we will keep or delete your Account based on this Agreement. You hereby commit and undertake the following: \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tYou understand and agree that the Site is an application service product. You shall take full responsibilities for the authenticity, legality, accuracy and validity of your registration information; you shall not post any information in the name of others; you shall not use registered accounts maliciously; otherwise, we reserve the right to suspend the Services and you shall fully bear all legal liability. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tYou shall use the Site and Services in accordance with all applicable laws and take all responsibility for activities under your registered Accounts, including your statements and any loss or damage that may directly or indirectly arise from your statements. You should estimate the risks of the content on your own and take all risks from it, including the risk that lies on the correctness, integrity or practicability of the content. Coolpad will not take any responsibility for any losses or damages that result from this behavior or activity; \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tYou have the obligation to take good care of the registration information on the Site and are responsible for all the activities. You must immediately notify Coolpad if you find any illegal or unauthorized activities. Coolpad will not be liable for damages or losses arising from a user’s non-compliance with any of the provision(s) above; \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tAll your statements on the Site are public information that any third party has access to. Any statement posted on the Site will be deemed as public information, and user should bear legal liability for this action. If you do not want any third party to get your statements, please do not post them on the Site. \r\n

\n1.2. You shall also understand and hereby acknowledge the following: \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tThe user accepts that, due to business development, we may change, suspend, restrict, terminate or revoke the rights of our services at any time without notice;\r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tWe may include advertisements, etc. in our Services. You agree to the display of advertisements and other events from us or our related parties or cooperators while enjoying our Services;\r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tWe have the right to suspend, at our sole discretion or determination, any content that violates the laws and regulations in any jurisdiction or the terms of this Agreement; that infringes, prejudices, threatens any right or safety; or that impersonates others. We also retain the right to take proper legal actions, including but not limited to removing any illegal or infringing content, suspending the qualification of violators and saving relative information and reporting to relevant authorities based on the applicable laws and regulations; \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tSome of our Services have to be used with other networks, including but not limited to the application market and the theme market. You shall bear all the related communication fees or fees from any third party service providers (including but not limited to China Telecom, China Mobile, etc.). We strongly advise you to contact your providers for related fees if there are value-added services involved in your activities; \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tYou hereby consent that Cool Cloud, our online cloud service provider (please visit www.coolyun.com for details), may analyze your phone contacts to search for your friends who also use Cool Cloud. For the use of Cool Cloud, please note that the relevant privacy policy and user agreement specific to Cool Cloud shall be understood and agreed. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tWhen you shop on the Site, you can only modify one of the following information for maintaining the account’s safety: your name, address or phone number. If you need any help, please call customer service using the phone number you put in the order. Any call from any number other than in the order requires confirmation. \r\n

\n<b>2. User Content</b>\r\n2.1. User Content refers to all the content (your information, picture, music or others) resulting from downloads, releases or other activities through the Site and Coolpad Services. You are solely responsible for such content, and bear all risks that result from your disclosure of such User Content. \r\n
2.2. Once you upload, release or engage in activities through the Site and Coolpad Services, you automatically grant to Coolpad an irrevocable, non-exclusive, sub-licensable, transferrable and royalty-free global licence to: \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tProvide you with Coolpad products and services or for the purposes of improving Coolpad products and services through our use of User Content. We may also copy, publish, display, make derivative works and/or bring it to other works, or use your user Account (except for your personal information) in other ways; and you authorize us the transferrable permission for the preceding subject matters; \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tCopy and publish your content and personal information only to designated receiver; you agree that you irrevocably waive any and all ownership, legal and moral rights to your user content. \r\n

\n<b>3. Rights and Obligations</b>\r\n3.1. You have the right to use the Site legally. \r\n

\n3.2. You have the right to upload, download, install, and use Coolpad products and services on mobile communication devices. \r\n

\n3.3. Coolpad and its affiliates possess the ownership of the Cool Cloud Accounts. You have the right to use Cool Cloud Accounts after you complete your registration. The rights to use Cool Cloud Accounts only belong to you, and you are not allowed to borrow, lease, license, transfer, gift or sell Cool Cloud Accounts. Coolpad has the right to retrieve any Account for operational needs. \r\n

\n3.4. You have the right to change and remove personal information, registered information, and any content posted. Please note that you have to take the risk that any picture or word saved in the system might also be deleted when you remove related information. \r\n

\n3.5. You are responsible for the safety of your Account information and password, and should bear legal liability for activities under registered Accounts. You agree not to use the passwords and Accounts of others under any circumstances. You agree to immediately notify Coolpad once you suspect others using your password or Account. \r\n

\n3.6. Rights limitations and restrictions\r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tYou shall not sell, lease, transfer, release or make other commercial use of the content from the Site or Coolpad products and services (including but not limited to the content or the advertisements or sponsored content); \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tYou shall not visit the Site or use Coolpad Services to establish similar or competitive services; \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tUnless expressly prescribed by laws, you shall not copy, publish, download, change, translate, merge, decompose, and paste or decompile etc. any part of the Site or Coolpad Services (including but not limited to the content or the advertisements or sponsored content) in any manner; \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tYou agree to bear all the risks and take full legal liability for the following activities while using the Site or Services: Opposing the basic principles determined in the Constitution of the People\'s Republic of China; endangering national security, leaking state secrets, subverting the government, and undermining national unity; harming national honor and interests; inciting ethnic hatred or ethnic discrimination, and undermining national unity; undermining national religious policy, promoting cults and superstitions; spreading rumor, disturbing social order, undermining social stability; spreading obscenity, pornography, gambling, violence, murder, terrorism or instigating others to commit crimes; insulting or slandering others, infringing upon the legal rights and interests of others; all other content prohibited by the administrative regulations and laws; \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tYou shall not use the Site or Coolpad Services to engage in any behavior or activity stated below: Upload or release virus, worm, and malware to damage or change computer system or data; collect the information or data of other users, such as email address, without authorization; disable network connection of the Site, put too much burden on the Site, interrupt or undermine the website server and connection in other ways; attempt to visit the Site, Cool Cloud, our server or the Site connection without authorization; interrupt or undermine other users\' normal use of the Coolpad Services. \r\n

\n<b>4. Third Party</b>\r\n4.1 You understand and agree that our services are based on technical support from third parties such as Android, etc. You understand that this Agreement is entered into between you and Coolpad. Coolpad shall be solely responsible for the content, maintenance, support services and guaranties generated and legal proceedings arising from the Site and Coolpad Services. You agree and authorize the Site and Services to limit your rights of using the Site and Cool Cloud services. \r\n

\n4.2 User Content refers to all the content (your information, picture, music or others) resulting from downloads, releases or other activities through the Site and Coolpad Services. You are solely responsible for such content, and bear all risks that result from your disclosure of such User Content. \r\n

\n4.3 When you visit the websites and advertisement of a third party, the third party’s terms and policy applies. You will bear all risks and legal responsibility when you use third party’s services. \r\n

\n4.4 The Site and Coolpad Services include content provided by other users; and the interaction between you and other users only belongs to you and other users. Coolpad does not control such User Content, bear legal liability, or own the obligations to check, monitor, examine and approve such User Content. You thus bear legal liability for the risks of such interaction. \r\n

\n<b>5. Liability for our Services</b>\r\n5.1. You agree to use the Site or Services harmlessly and help Coolpad to avoid bearing any lawsuit, complaint, loss, damage, responsibility, cost and fees (including but not limited to counsel fees) from any third party caused by the use of the Site or Services, your user content, or your violation of this Agreement. \r\n

\n5.2. User Content refers to all the content (your information, picture, music or others) resulting from downloads, releases or other activities through the Site and Coolpad Services. You are solely responsible for such content, and bear all risks that result from your disclosure of such User Content. \r\n

\n5.3. You will not unilaterally reconcile when you and Coolpad jointly file a lawsuit against any third party without written consent from Coolpad. \r\n

\n5.4. Coolpad will reasonably notify you such lawsuit or action at law. \r\n

\n5.5. Under no circumstances will Coolpad bear any indirect, consequential, exemplary, incidental, exceptional or punitive compensation liability resulting from this Agreement. You bear all the risks from using the computer system and mobile database through the Site or Services. \r\n

\n<b>6. Disclaimer of Warranty</b>\r\n6.1. Coolpad will not bear any legal liability under circumstances stated below: \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tProvide your personal information requested by government departments or the laws; \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tDisclose private information caused by your negligent actions; \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tAny circumstances caused by suspension, breakdown and so on that result from the hacking, virus invasion, blockings due to illegal and harassing content, government control or any other reasons related to network, technique, communication line and information security management; \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tCause losses to the users because of any third party issues, such as the communication line breakdown, technical problems, the network and computer breakdown, and other cases of force majeure; \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tRisks come from threat, defamation, offensive or illegal information that caused by anonymous or percolation through the Site or Coolpad Services; \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tAny psychological or physical suffer and economic losses due to misleading or deceiving when you interact with others through the Site or Coolpad Services. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tThe Site or Coolpad Services expressively declare that we do not guarantee timeliness, security and accuracy of the Services expressly, impliedly or in other forms. The Services include but not limited to: The “Intelligent Phone Number Recognition” Service, which refers to the service that recognize phone numbers that come from incoming and outgoing calls or text messages. Coolpad will upload such number to its server, therefore identify the “Marked Information” of such number. Your data and information in this Service will be strictly protected, and we make sure you cannot be identified result from uploading such information. Such Marked Information is provided by users or network partners. We use technical means to ensure that (i) such Marked Information is consistent with the information uploaded by many users during a period of time (i.e., when the tag information of a strange phone number is “a fraud telephone marked by 500 people”, it indicates that a large number of users determine the number of telephone is a fraud and update the Marked Information within a period of time); (ii) filter and select the most reliable Marked Information, and indicate the sources of such information to you. Meanwhile, we provide the option for users to send us feedback on Marked Information. \r\n

\n6.2. Any content posted by the user on the Site does not represent or reflect any viewpoint or policy of Coolpad; Coolpad does not bear any responsibility for this. \r\n

\n6.3. Under no circumstances shall Coolpad bear any responsibility for any indirect, consequential, exemplary, incidental, exceptional or punitive damages, including profit losses caused by using Coolpad’s Services. Notwithstanding any provisions contained herein to the contrary, the responsibilities we bear will not exceed the fees (if any) you pay for Coolpad Services during registration valid period, for any reason or in any manner. \r\n

\n<b>7. Intellectual Property</b>\r\n7.1. All text, picture, image, audio and/or video information contained in the Web services provided by Coolpad shall be protected by copyright, trademark and/or other property ownership laws. Without the consent of related owners, the above-mentioned information shall not be used for any commercial purposes. \r\n

\n7.2. All information used in the Web services provided by Coolpad including but not limited to any image, picture, animation, video, audio, music, words and additional procedures, as well as attached help information contained in software belong to the corresponding software copyright owner. Without the permission of the copyright owner, you may not reverse engineer, decompile or disassemble the software. \r\n

\n7.3. Any information posted on the Site or the interactive platform shall not infringe the intellectual property of any third party. You cannot upload, release, change, spread or copy any information or trademark under copyright protection, or proprietary information of others, without the prior written consent of the owners. If Coolpad receives the appropriate notice from any copyright owner or its legal representative, we will remove the related content after investigation. \r\n

\n7.4. Graphics, words and composition involved in Coolpad Services and Coolpad logos, product and service name are the trademarks of Coolpad. Without the prior written consent, you cannot display or use them in other manners in any way. By no means can any entity or individual use, copy, change, spread, transcribe any part of the trademark or sell with other products. \r\n

\n7.5. In addition to the foregoing provisions, you can promptly contact us if you think someone copies or publishes your work on the Site, and also infringe your copyright. Please also include the following information in the written notice: \r\n
(i) materials evidencing that you have copyright or you are authorized to exercise copyright of the allegedly infringing content; (ii) your explicit identification, address and contact information; (iii) the network address of the allegedly infringing content; (iv) the description of the allegedly infringing copyright works; (v) materials evidencing that your copyright infringed; (vi) under the premise that you agree to bear all consequences of perjury, you issue written statement of the accuracy and authenticity of the content in your written notice. \r\n

\n<b>8. Modification and Termination</b>\r\n8.1. Modification\r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tWe may change or modify terms of this Agreement at any time, and will notify you through your email address or notifications on the Site. Your use of the Site and Coolpad Services after modifications to the terms indicate that you agree to such changes; \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tCoolpad reserves the right to modify, keep and suspend the Site and Coolpad Services without notification from time to time; \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tYou agree that Coolpad will not take any responsibility for changing, reserving or suspending the Site and Coolpad Services. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tAny updated version of the Site or any future version, update or other changes of Coolpad Services shall be bound by this Agreement. \r\n

\n8.2. Termination\r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tThis Agreement becomes valid and stays valid during your use of the Site and Coolpad Services, until the termination according to this Agreement. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tNotwithstanding the foregoing provisions, this Agreement becomes effective the first time you use the Site and Coolpad Services if that happens before you accept this Agreement. This stays valid unless the early termination applies. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tWe may reserve your right to access the Site, Coolpad Services, and your account; we may terminate this Agreement at any time for any reason without notice, as believe you violate our acceptable policies or other terms of this Agreement. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tNot subject to the preceding provisions, Coolpad reserves the right to terminate this Agreement if the user infringe the copyright of the third party and receive the notice from the owner or legal representative of the owner. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tOnce this Agreement terminated, all your website accounts and your right to use the Site and Coolpad Services will also be terminated. You shall understand this means your User Content will be removed from our database. Coolpad will not take any responsibility for terminating this Agreement, including terminating your user account and removing your User Content. \r\n

\n<b>9. Miscellaneous</b>\r\n9.1. Feedback\r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tYour suggestion to Coolpad (“Feedback”) is regarded as transferring all rights of Feedback; Coolpad has the right to use the Feedback in any appropriate method. We also consider this feedback unclassified and non-exclusive. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tYou agree not to provide any information you regard as private and proprietary to Coolpad. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tWe reserve the rights (not obligations) to examine your content on our judgments. We have the right to delete or remove your content at any time for any reason. According to the terms of Modification and Termination, we have the right to reserve or terminate your account (including but not limited to your Cool Cloud account). \r\n

\n9.2. Privacy Policy\r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tPlease review our Privacy Policy, which has equivalent rights with and is indivisible to this Agreement. Coolpad has the right to analyze and commercially use the whole user database on the premise of non-disclosure of privacy information of individual users. \r\n

\n9.3. Notification
\t<b>•</b>\tYou must provide the latest, most used and valid email address. Coolpad will not take any responsibility if we are unable to reach you through the email address you provide. Undoubtedly, the notifications on the Site and emails sent to you are valid notifications. \r\n

\n9.4. Applicable Law\r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tThis Agreement shall be governed and interpreted according to the laws of PRC. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tAny dispute between you and Coolpad shall first be settled through friendly consultation. If no agreement is reached, the dispute shall be submitted to the jurisdiction court where Yulong Computer Telecommunication Scientific (Shenzhen) Co., Ltd., a subsidiary of Coolpad Group, is located. \r\n

\n9.5. Independence\r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tIf some provisions of this Agreement cannot be applied for some reasons, they will be revised to apply legally; and other provisions remain applicable. \r\n

\n9.6. Integrality\r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tThis Agreement (including the Privacy Policy) is the ultimate, integral and exclusive agreement between you and Coolpad, in relation to any matter relating to the Site and Coolpad Services, which supersedes and combines all the previous negotiations and agreements regarding to such matters (including End User License Agreement and Terms of Service) . \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tThe title of each paragraph is written only for the convenience of reading and does not have any legal or contractual obligations. \r\n
\t<b>•</b>\tWithout written consent from Coolpad, you cannot transfer the rights and obligations stated in this Agreement. Any behavior or activity violating the provision about such a transfer attempt is invalid. \r\n

\n<b>10. Contact Us</b>\r\nThe copyright of this Policy belongs to the Coolpad Group. Coolpad Group reserves the right to interpret and change it. If you have any questions, comments, or suggestions on our products, please submit them by calling customer service hotline at 4008881388 or visiting www.coolpad.com.</string>
</resources>